A Guide to the Records of Julian A. Burruss, President, Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1906-1946
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Series 6: Subject Files
  - Subseries 1: Subject Files, 1919-1928
    - Military Report - R.O.T.C., 1919-1922 (Box-folder 32-1905)
    - Mimeographs & Printed Material, 1920's, 1930's (Box-folder 32-1906)
    - Mimeograph Material, 1928 (Box-folder 32-1907)
    - Misc.-Memos, Correspondences, 1928 (Box-folder 32-1908)
    - Misc. Mimeograph Letters to Faculty & Students, 1920s (Box-folder 32-1909)
    - Misc. Letters to Patrons & Students, 1920s (Box-folder 32-1910)
    - Money Statistics, 1920s (Box-folder 32-1911)
    - Nat. Assoc. of Commercial Organization Secretaries, 1928 (Box-folder 32-1912)
    - Needs, 1921-23 (Box-folder 32-1913)
    - New York, University of, 1922 (Box-folder 32-1914)
    - Office Employees, 1920s (Box-folder 32-1915)
    - Organizational Chart, 1920-21 (Box-folder 32-1916)
    - Orientation, 1920 (Box-folder 32-1917)
    - Payrolls, 1918-1921 (Box-folder 32-1918)
    - Petition Vocational Students, 1922 (Box-folder 32-1919)
    - Plant Pathology - Annual Report, 1920s (Box-folder 32-1920)
    - Poultry Testing (3 folders) (Box-folder 32-1921, 32-1921A, 32-1921B)
    - Pre-Med Course, 1920s (Box-folder 32-1922)
    - Presidential Powers, 1921 (Box-folder 32-1923)
    - Publicity Organization, 1928 (Box-folder 32-1924)
    - Purnell Bill, 1920s (Box-folder 32-1925)
    - Religious Education, 1927 (Box-folder 32-1926)
    - Resignation - Why?, 1923-1924 (Box-folder 32-1927)
    - Resolutions, 1924 (Box-folder 32-1928)
    - Rockefeller, Laura Spelman, Fund, 1926-27 (Box-folder 32-1929)
    - Salaries, 1919, 1925 (Box-folder 32-1930)
    - Regarding Salaries of US Army Officers, 1928 (Box-folder 32-1931)
    - Sanitary Board, 1920-23 (Box-folder 32-1932)
    - Shenandoah National Park, 1920s (Box-folder 32-1933)
    - Scott Case, 1923 (Box-folder 32-1934)
      - Cadet John Scott was expelled for refusing to comply with unfair punishment. 130 cadet officers and non-commissioned officers resigned in protest. Includes letters from parents.
    - Semi-Centennial, 1922 (Box-folder 32-1935)
    - Special Education Commission, Dr. M.V. O'Shea, 1920s (Box-folder 32-1936)
    - Staff Promotions, 1920s (Box-folder 32-1937)
    - Statistical Studies - President's Office, 1928 (Box-folder 32-1938)
    - Stream Pollution Matters, 1911-28 (Box-folder 32-1939)
    - Student Life Report, 1920s (Box-folder 32-1940)
    - Student Pranks, 1923 (Box-folder 32-1941)
    - Students, 1921-1922 (Box-folder 33-1942)
    - Students, 1922-1923 (Box-folder 33-1943)
      - letter Re: women students and 'ladies retiring room'
    - Students, 1924-1925 (Box-folder 33-1944)
    - Students, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 33-1945)
    - Students, 1926-1927 (Box-folder 33-1946)
    - Students, 1927-1928 (Box-folder 33-1947)
    - Summer School, 1923-1925 (Box-folder 33-1948)
    - Teachers Insurance & Annuity Association, 1926 (Box-folder 33-1949)
    - Teaching Loads, 1921 (Box-folder 33-1950)
    - Teaching Loads, 1920s (Box-folder 33-1951)
    - Teaching Load Blanks, 1926-1927 (Box-folder 33-1952)
    - Teaching Load Blanks, 1927-1928 (Box-folder 33-1953)
    - Telegrams, 1926 (Box-folder 33-1954)
    - Telegrams, 1927-1928 (Box-folder 33-1955)
    - Treasurer, 1920 (Box-folder 33-1956)
    - Governor Trinkle, 1924 (Box-folder 33-1957)
    - VA Education Survey, 1927 (Box-folder 33-1958)
    - VA Education Survey, 1927-1928 (Box-folder 33-1959)
    - VA Education Survey Development & Suggestions, 10/26/27 (Box-folder 33-1960)
    - Welsch Bill H.R. 5838 Military Affairs Committee, 1920s (Box-folder 33-1961)
    - Workmen's Compensation, 1927 (Box-folder 33-1962)
  - Subseries 2: Subject Files, 1928-1931
    - Aeronautics, 1927-1930 (Box-folder 33-1963)
    - Agricultural Conference Board, 1929 (Box-folder 33-1964)
    - Airport, 1929-1931 (Box-folder 33-1965)
    - Alcohol Reports: Commission of Internal Revenue, 1931 (Box-folder 33-1966)
      - Industrial alcohol government policy and problems relating to manufacture, storage, distribution, and sale of alcohol in the arts and industries
      - Alcohol use at VT
    - American Chamber of Agriculture (Atlanta), 1/30/1929 (Box-folder 33-1967)
    - American Mining Congress, 1930-31 (Box-folder 33-1968)
    - American Political Science Association, 1931 (Box-folder 33-1969)
    - American Society of Mechanical Engineers, 1930-31 (Box-folder 33-1970)
    - Band director, 1931 (Box-folder 33-1971)
    - Biennial Budget Requests, 1928-1930 (Box-folder 33-1972)
    - Boy Scouts, 1931 (Box-folder 33-1973)
    - Copper-Ketchan Act, 1928-1931 (Box-folder 33-1974)
    - Child Welfare Conference, 1931 (Box-folder 33-1975)
      - Virginia Rural Child Welfare Program
    - Changes in Organization, of Curricula, etc., 1931 (Box-folder 33-1976)
    - Conservation & Development Commission- - Mead Flippin, Hodges, & Others, 1926-31 (Box-folder 33-1977)
    - County Agent List of Farmers, 1929 (Box-folder 33-1978)
    - Compulsory Church Attendance, Dean of Men, 1928-30 (Box-folder 33-1979)
      - House Bill 360, Prohibiting Hazing at School.
      - Quality Credit Averages for Students from 1931-1932.
    - Commission List, etc., 1929 (Box-folder 33-1980)
    - Dairy Products Bldg, 1930 (Box-folder 33-1981)
    - Dairy Husbandry building, 1931 (Box-folder 33-1982)
      - Expenses
    - Drought situation, 1930 (Box-folder 33-1983)
    - Education Commission recommendations, 1931 (Box-folder 33-1984)
      - Virginia Education Commission recommendations
    - Engineering Extension - Registration, 1930-31 (Box-folder 33-1985)
    - Eng. Experiment Station - McNary Bill, 1929-30 (Box-folder 33-1986)
    - Faculty Meeting, 1924-29 (Box-folder 33-1987)
      - Harvard Officials Ban Discrimination.
      - Study of Records in Regard to Scholarships for Juniors and Seniors.
    - Financial Agents, 1930s (Box-folder 33-1988)
    - Folders, etc., Other Colleges, 1931 (Box-folder 33-1989)
    - General Survey, 1930-31 (Box-folder 33-1990)
    - Heating and power plant, 1928-1931 (Box-folder 34-1991)
    - Heating Buildings, 1930-31 (Box-folder 34-1992)
    - High School boys and girls and others, 1925-1931 (Box-folder 34-1993)
    - Hospital addition, 1929 (Box-folder 34-1994)
    - Illiteracy campaign, 1931 (Box-folder 34-1995)
      - Teaching of illiterate women
    - Industrial Committee of State Chamber of Commerce, 1931 (Box-folder 34-1996)
    - Chamber of Commerce Industry Committee, 1931 (Box-folder 34-1997)
    - Institute of Rural Affairs, 1929 (Box-folder 34-1998)
    - Inspection Trip, 1931 (Box-folder 34-1999)
    - Interracial Cooperation, Commission on, 1931-34 (Box-folder 34-2000)
    - Interest on Federal Funds-Correspondence, 1933 (Box-folder 34-2001)
    - Invitations to J. Burruss, 1931 (2 folders) (Box-folder 34-2002 to 34-2002A)
    - Janitor's Training School, 1931 (Box-folder 34-2003)
    - Keller-Invitations, 1931 (Box-folder 34-2004)
    - Lamme Award, Prof. Pritchard, 1929 (Box-folder 34-2005)
    - McCormick Centennial, 7/29/31 (2 folders) (Box-folder 34-2006 to 34-2007)
    - McCormick Centennial Hotel & Transpo. Matters, 1931 (Box-folder 34-2008)
    - McCormick Family, 1931 (Box-folder 34-2009)
    - McCormick Centennial faculty correspondence, 1931 (Box-folder 34-2010)
    - McCormick Day, 7/29/31 (Box-folder 34-2011)
    - McCormick mailing list, 1931 (Box-folder 34-2012)
    - Mechanical Engineering Laboratory, 1930 (Box-folder 34-2013)
    - Mechanical Lab, 1930 (Box-folder 34-2014)
    - Military Camp Leaves, 1931 (Box-folder 34-2015)
    - National Advisory Committee on Education, 1930-31 (Box-folder 34-2016)
    - Noell Act Loans, 1930 (Box-folder 34-2017)
    - Physics, 1930 (Box-folder 34-2018)
    - Quality Credit Averages, 1925-30 (Box-folder 34-2019)
      - Percentage of passes for class levels.
    - Radio Matters - radio broadcasting, 1928-1930 (Box-folder 34-2020)
    - Rural Electrification Matters, 1929 (Box-folder 34-2021)
    - Salary Increases, 1931 (Box-folder 34-2022)
    - Sewage - Road Grading, 1927-29 (Box-folder 34-2023)
    - Social Activities Committee, 1940-42, 1946-47 (Box-folder 34-2024)
    - Soft Wheat Flour Matters, 1929 (Box-folder 34-2025)
    - Southern Association of College, 1923-1931 (Box-folder 34-2026)
    - Southern Commercial Secretaries Association, 1929 (Box-folder 34-2027)
    - Stable Money Association, 1931 (Box-folder 34-2028)
    - State Scholarship Certificate to Mildred Fanning, 1930 (Box-folder 35-2029)
    - State Supported Institutions' Conferences, 10/9/1931-1/22/1932 (Box-folder 35-2030)
    - Students, 1929-1930 (Box-folder 35-2031)
    - Students, 1931 (Box-folder 35-2032)
    - Summer Activities, 1929 (Box-folder 35-2033)
    - Summer Quarter, 1929 (2 folders) (Box-folder 35-2034 to 35-2034A)
    - Taxation, 1931 (Box-folder 35-2035)
    - Teaching Load Blanks, 1928-1929 (Box-folder 35-2036)
    - University of Illinois Rating, 1926-29 (Box-folder 35-2037)
    - Virginia Mechanical Institute (H.L. Davidson), 1930-1931 (Box-folder 35-2038)
    - College water supply, 1928-1931 (Box-folder 35-2039)
    - Liberal Arts College for Women in Harrisonburg (State Teachers College), 1931 (Box-folder 35-2040)
  - Subseries 3: Subject Files, 1927-1946
    - AAU, 1940 (Box-folder 35-2041)
    - Academic Reports, 1935-40 (Box-folder 35-2042)
    - Academic Reports, 1941-46 (Box-folder 35-2043)
    - Accelerated Programs, 1942 (Box-folder 35-2044)
    - "Speeding-Up" Curricula (Accelerated Program), 1942 (Box-folder 35-2045)
    - Administration, Council on, 1939-40 (Box-folder 35-2046)
    - Advisory Legislative Council, Committee of VA/Purchase & Printing Laws, 1937 (Box-folder 35-2047)
    - Aero Accounts, 1940-41 (Box-folder 35-2048)
    - National Aero Association, 1936 (Box-folder 35-2049)
    - Notes on Aeronautical Engineering, 1942 (Box-folder 35-2050)
    - Aeronautics, 1942-43 (Box-folder 35-2051)
    - Aeronautics, Dept. of, Operations Handbook, 1941-43 (Box-folder 35-2052)
    - Aeronautics, Dept. of, 1944 (Box-folder 35-2053)
    - Aeronautics, 1944-45 (Box-folder 35-2054)
    - Agricultural Advisory Council, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 35-2055)
    - Agricultural Curricula Revision, 1933 (Box-folder 35-2056)
    - Agricultural Economics Fellowships, 1936 (Box-folder 35-2057)
    - Agricultural Economics Dept. Library, 1939-40 (Box-folder 35-2058)
    - Agricultural Experiment Station - Hofmann, 1942 (Box-folder 35-2059)
    - Airport, 1931 (Box-folder 35-2060)
    - Airport, VPI, Committee, 1930-31 (Box-folder 35-2061)
    - Airport, VPI July 1, 1935 (Box-folder 35-2062)
    - Airport, VPI, 1935-36 (Box-folder 35-2063)
    - Airport, VPI, 1937 (Box-folder 35-2064)
    - Airport, VPI, 1939 (Box-folder 35-2065)
    - Airport, VPI, 1940 (Box-folder 35-2066)
    - Airport Property, VPI, 1940-41 (Box-folder 36-2067)
    - Airport, VPI, Director, Wright, J.H., 1940-41 (Box-folder 36-2068)
    - Corr. - Burruss, Wright, Norris/Airport Matters, 1940-42 (Box-folder 36-2069)
    - Airport, VPI/Purchase of Land for 1/42-7/42 (Box-folder 36-2070)
    - Airport, VPI/Development Project, 1942-43 (Box-folder 36-2071)
    - Airport, VPI, 7/1/42-7/1/43 (Box-folder 36-2072)
    - Airport Investigating Committee, 1944 (Box-folder 36-2073)
    - A.B.C. Board, 1934 (Box-folder 36-2074)
      - College Community Voted "dry."
      - Alcohol Beverage Control Board.
    - Allotments for Expenditure, Authorized by Gov., 1939-42 (Box-folder 36-2075)
    - Allotments, 1943-44 (Box-folder 36-2076)
    - Alpha Zeta Fraternity, 1932 (Box-folder 36-2077)
    - Aluminum Campaign Material, 1941 (Box-folder 36-2078)
    - Alumni, 1929-36 (Box-folder 36-2079)
    - Alumni Records, 1929-32 (Box-folder 36-2080)
    - Alumni, 1938-44 (Box-folder 36-2081)
    - Alumni, 1942 (Box-folder 36-2082)
    - Alumni Conference, 4/29/33 (Box-folder 36-2083)
    - Alumni Conference, 1933 (Box-folder 36-2084)
      - Alumni Conference Report.
      - Total Enrollment Figures for Virginia Students in Virginia Colleges for the Year, 1930-1931.
      - Figures for Permanent and Current Assets for 1931-1932.
      - Enrollment, Salaries, Income Statistics.
      - Enrollment by Curricula in Virginia State Institutions.
      - Schedule of Changes and Fees for Students at Virginia State Colleges.
      - "Education" in the State Budget.
      - Summary of Questionnaire Concerning Finances of Land-Grant Institutions Under New Conditions.
      - Commonwealth of Virginia Total Revenues and Expenditures for Fiscal Year End June 1932.
      - College Preference Survey of College Seniors in 1932.
    - Alumni Killed in Action - Letters to Relatives, 1945-46 (Box-folder 36-2085)
    - American Chemical Society Report, 1938 (Box-folder 36-2086)
    - American Council on Education, 1924-29 (Box-folder 36-2087)
    - American Council on Education, 1930-35 (Box-folder 36-2088)
    - American Council on Education, 1936-41 (Box-folder 36-2089)
    - American Society of Agricultural Engineers, 1938 (Box-folder 36-2090)
    - Appalachian Forest Research Council, 1931-35 (Box-folder 36-2091)
    - Dept. of Architectural Engineering March, 1933 (Box-folder 37-2092)
    - Audit of Army Specialized Training Program, 3/8/1943-6/30/1944 (Box-folder 37-2093)
    - A.S.T.P. - General, 1943 (Box-folder 37-2094)
    - Misc.-List of Assets, etc., 1935 (Box-folder 37-2095)
    - Association of Colleges & Secondary Schools of Southern States, 1933-35 (Box-folder 37-2096)
    - Association of Land Grant Colleges, 1923-33 (Box-folder 37-2097)
    - Land Grant College Survey, 1927-29 (Box-folder 37-2098)
    - Association of Land Grant C's & U's, 1929-38 (Box-folder 37-2099)
    - Association of Land Grant Colleges (Experiment Station Record), 1930 (Box-folder 37-2100)
    - Association of Land Grant Colleges (Retirement & Group Insurance), 1932-36 (Box-folder 37-2101)
    - L.G.C.A. Committee, 1933-34 (Box-folder 37-2102)
    - Association of Land Grant C's & U's, 1933-40 (Box-folder 37-2103)
    - Land Grant College Association Committee on Organization & Policy, 1935-38 (Box-folder 37-2104)
    - Land Grant College (Answers to Questions), 1936 (Box-folder 37-2105)
    - Land Grant College (Answers to Questions), 1937 (Box-folder 37-2106)
    - Land Grant College Association, 1937 (Box-folder 37-2107)
    - L.G.C.A. Committee on Rating Profess'l Schools, 1937 (Box-folder 37-2108)
    - Association of Land Grant Colleges & Universities, 1937-38 (2 folders) (Box-folder 37-2109 to 37-2110)
    - L.G.C.A., 1937-38 (2 folders) (Box-folder 37-2111 to 37-2111A)
    - L.G.C.A. Committee on College Organization & Policy, 1937-40 (Box-folder 37-2112)
    - Association of Land Grant Colleges & Universities, 1938 (Box-folder 37-2113)
    - Association of Land Grant Colleges, 1941-45 (Box-folder 37-2114)
    - Association of Military Colleges, 1923-40 (Box-folder 38-2115)
    - Association of University & Col. Business Officers of the US, 1922-40 (Box-folder 38-2116)
    - Athletic Association, 1920-1940 (Box-folder 38-2117)
    - Athletic Association (Business, Salaries, Bookstore, etc.), 1940 (Box-folder 38-2118)
    - Athletic Fee, 1927-34 (Box-folder 38-2119)
      - Proposed Faculty Censorship of Student Publications.
    - Athletics, 1936 (Box-folder 38-2120)
      - Southern Conference Association, Constitution and By-Laws.
      - Athletic Scholarship Information.
    - Audit, by state, 1934-35 (Box-folder 38-2121)
    - Aviation - Nonactive file, 1939 (Box-folder 38-2122)
    - Aviation Training, 1939-42 (Box-folder 38-2123)
    - B-Miscellaneous, 1937-38 (Box-folder 38-2124)
    - Bang's Disease in Beef Cattle Herd, 1937 (Box-folder 38-2125)
    - Bank of Blacksburg - Financing - Bonds & Other Revenue - Advertising - 1st Nat'l Exchg Bank, 1938-40 (Box-folder 38-2126)
    - A "Bill," 1930-32 (Box-folder 38-2127)
    - Biological Survey, U.S., Game Management, 1934-36 (2 folders) (Box-folder 38-2128 to 38-2128A)
    - Blacksburg Community Federation, 1931-32 (Box-folder 38-2129)
    - Town of Blacksburg, 1936-38 (Box-folder 38-2130)
    - Blacksburg Protest, 1934 (Box-folder 38-2131)
      - Proceedings of the hearing before the Committee of the Board of Visitors
    - Blueprints/Maps/Airport/Burruss Hall, 1940 (Box-folder 38-2132)
    - Bonds - Payments 1284-F, 1938-39 (Box-folder 38-2133)
    - Bradford, J.H., Personnel Director/Budget Director, 1944 (Box-folder 38-2134)
    - Budget Adjustments, 1931-32 (Box-folder 38-2135)
    - Budget Adjustments, 1932-33 (Box-folder 38-2136)
    - Budget, 1933-34 (Box-folder 38-2137)
    - Budget, Working, Reductions, 1933-34 (Box-folder 38-2138)
    - Working Budget, 1933-34 (Box-folder 39-2139)
    - Special Budget Allotments, 1934 (Box-folder 39-2140)
    - President's Statement on State Audit, 1932-34 (Box-folder 38-2141)
    - Budget of Request, 1934-36 (Box-folder 39-2142)
    - Budget, 1934-35 (Box-folder 39-2143)
    - Working Budget, 1935-36 (Box-folder 39-2144)
    - Working Budget, 1936-37 (Box-folder 39-2145)
    - Request Budget, 1936-38 (Box-folder 39-2146)
    - Budget Requests, 1937-38 (Box-folder 39-2147)
    - Budget Requests, 1938-39 (Box-folder 39-2148)
    - Budget Requests, 1939-40 (Box-folder 39-2149)
    - Request Budget, 1940-42 (Box-folder 39-2150)
    - Biennial Budget Hearings, 1940-42 (Box-folder 39-2151)
    - Budget, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 39-2152)
    - Budget Requests, 1942-44 (Box-folder 39-2153)
    - Biennial Budget of Requests, 1942-44 (Box-folder 39-2154)
    - Biennial Budget, 1944-46 (Box-folder 39-2155)
    - Working Budget, 1939-40 (Box-folder 39-2156)
    - Working Budget, 1940-41 (Box-folder 39-2157)
    - Working Budget, 1941-42 (Box-folder 39-2158)
    - Working Budget, 1942-43 (Box-folder 39-2159)
    - Working Budget, 1943-44 (Box-folder 39-2160)
    - Working Budget, 1944-45 (Box-folder 39-2161)
    - Budget: 6-year Capital Improvement Program, 1942-46 (Box-folder 39-2162)
    - Budget, 1920-1921 (Box-folder 39-2163)
    - Bugle, 1932 (Box-folder 39-2164)
    - Bureau of Agricultural Economics, 1938-39 (Box-folder 39-2165)
    - Office of Business Manager, 1947 (Box-folder 39-2166)
    - Dr. Cammack's Charges, 1935 (Box-folder 40-2167)
    - Candidates for Degree- -March & Leaves Reg., 1943 (Box-folder 40-2168)
    - Capital Outlaw Program, 1944 (Box-folder 40-2169)
    - Certificate of Merit Matters, 1924-35 (Box-folder 40-2170)
    - Certificate of Merit Matters, 1936-37 (Box-folder 40-2171)
    - Chamber of Commerce/State/R.F. Nelson, Director of Publicity, 1929-33 (Box-folder 40-2172)
    - Chamber of Commerce/State/Leroy Hodges, Managing Director, 1932-36 (Box-folder 40-2173)
    - Chamber of Commerce/State/Clarence W. Newman, Director of Membership, 1933-35 (Box-folder 40-2174)
    - Chamber of Commerce/State, 1935-43 (Box-folder 40-2175)
    - Church Services, 1936 (Box-folder 40-2176)
      - Issue of Required Church Attendance.
    - C.C.C. Camp, 1935 (Box-folder 40-2177)
      - Civilian Conservation Corp. Camp and Development of V.P.I. Campus-"Old Smithfield," State Park, Detailed Map.
    - Civil Works Administration, 1934 (Box-folder 40-2178)
    - A Plan for Class Cuts, 1940 (Box-folder 40-2179)
    - Coal, Refund on Freight, 1936-38 (Box-folder 40-2180)
    - Code of VA-Sections 853-869/Est. of College (Box-folder 40-2181)
    - College Steward, 1939 (Box-folder 40-2182)
    - Commandant-R.W. Wilson;Geo. Henderson, 1943-44 (Box-folder 40-2183)
    - Misc.-58th Annual Commencement, Smokeless Coal Company, etc., 1930 (Box-folder 40-2184)
    - Commencement, 1938-46 (Box-folder 40-2185)
    - Misc.-59th Annual Commencement, 1931 (Box-folder 40-2186)
    - Misc.-60th Annual Commencement, 1932 (Box-folder 40-2187)
    - Misc.-61st Annual Commencement, 1933 (Box-folder 40-2188)
    - Misc.-62nd Annual Commencement, 1934 (Box-folder 40-2189)
    - Misc.-63rd Annual Commencement, 1935 (Box-folder 40-2190)
    - Misc.-64th Annual Commencement, 1936 (Box-folder 40-2191)
    - Misc.-65th Annual Commencement, 1937 (Box-folder 40-2192)
    - Misc.-66th Annual Commencement, 1938 (Box-folder 40-2193)
    - Misc.-67th Annual Commencement, 1939 (Box-folder 40-2194)
    - Misc.-68th Annual Commencement, 1940 (Box-folder 40-2195)
    - Misc.-69th Annual Commencement, 1941 (Box-folder 40-2196)
    - Misc.-70th Annual Commencement, 1942 (Box-folder 40-2197)
    - Commencement, 1942-46 (Box-folder 40-2198)
    - Committee on C-op Radford State Teachers Coll., 1940 (Box-folder 40-2199)
    - Committee on Jobs, 1939 (Box-folder 40-2200)
    - Committee on Public Service Training, 1935-39 (Box-folder 40-2201)
    - Commonwealth of VA/Executive Order #69, 1942 (Box-folder 40-2202)
    - Conference of Virginia Secretaries, 1932 (Box-folder 40-2203)
    - Contracts before July, 1945 (Box-folder 40-2204)
    - Contracts - ASTP, 1943 (Box-folder 40-2205)
    - Cost Estimates, 1939-40 (Box-folder 40-2206)
    - Council on Public Administration, 1938-40 (Box-folder 40-2207)
    - Crumpacker, C.A., Farm, 1944 (Box-folder 40-2208)
    - Curtiss-Wright Contract, 1942 (Box-folder 40-2209)
    - Darden, Governor Colgate W., 1942 (Box-folder 40-2210)
    - Darden, Gov. Colgate W., 1942-44 (Box-folder 40-2211)
    - Declaration of Intent, 1940s (Box-folder 40-2212)
    - Dining Hall Operation, 1938-39 (Box-folder 41-2213)
    - Dining Hall, 1942-43 (Box-folder 41-2214)
    - Discipline, Readmission, Scholarship, Other Matters, 1930s-1940s (Box-folder 41-2215)
    - Educational Policies Commission, 1936 (Box-folder 41-2216)
    - Electricity, 1931-35 (Box-folder 41-2217)
      - Enlargement of Steam Boiler Plant.
      - Increase in Energy Demand by the Town of Blacksburg and V.P.I.
      - Proposed Changes in Generating Equipment.
    - Emergency Relief Administration Era, 1933 (Box-folder 41-2218)
    - Endowment Fund Investment, 1934-35 (Box-folder 41-2219)
    - Engineering Council for Professional Development, 1937 (Box-folder 41-2220)
    - Engineers' Council for Professional Development, 1941 (Box-folder 41-2221)
    - EDT Courses - Norfolk, 1941 (Box-folder 41-2222)
    - Eng. Exp. Sta., 1937-41 (Box-folder 41-2223)
    - English, Committee for Improvement of Undergraduate, 1938 (Box-folder 41-2224)
    - Enrollment of Students, 1932-37 (Box-folder 41-2225)
    - List of E.R.C. Students, 1943 (Box-folder 41-2226)
    - Misc.-Executive Bulletin, Virginia State Colleges, 1936 (Box-folder 41-2227)
    - Misc.-Executive Bulletin, List of Curriculums, etc., 1937-40 (Box-folder 41-2228)
    - Misc.-Exec Bulletin, Selective Service, Faculty Line, 1940-43 (Box-folder 41-2229)
    - Expenditures, 1940 (Box-folder 41-2230)
    - Expenditures, 1941-42 (Box-folder 41-2231)
    - Expenditures, 7/1/44-12/31/44 (Box-folder 41-2232)
    - Faculty Blank Letters, 1941 (Box-folder 41-2233)
    - Faculty Blanket Letter, 1943 (Box-folder 41-2234)
    - Faculty Changes, 1943 (Box-folder 41-2235)
    - Misc.-List of Faculty, etc., 1932 (Box-folder 41-2236)
    - Teaching Faculty, Oct. 15, 1943 (Box-folder 41-2237)
    - Faculty Center/CEC, 1928-32 (Box-folder 41-2238)
      - Need for new Buildings/Construction.
    - Faculty Apartments - Operation, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 41-2239)
    - Use of Faculty Dorm (Box-folder 21-2240)
    - Report on Farming Operations/Minority School Recommendations, 1941 (Box-folder 41-2241)
    - Federal Appropriations, 1921-36--including proposal for paving Main Street in Blacksburg (Box-folder 41-2242)
    - Federal Appropriations/Congressional, W.P.A., etc, 1936-41 (Box-folder 41-2243)
    - Federal Appropriations, 1944 (Box-folder 44-2244)
      - Agricultural Extension & Experiment Station, 1939-42
    - Federal Emergency Relief Administration Report, 1934 (Box-folder 41-2245)
    - F.E.R.A. Payroll, 1934-35 (Box-folder 41-2246)